NYSUT Publications 6174 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Advocate, Publication (Box 3)
  - Box: 3, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Item 7: Advocate, 1993; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.19:no.7 (1993:Apr.)
    - Item 8: Advocate, 1993; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.19:no.8 (1993:May)
    - Item 9: Advocate, 1993; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.19:no.9 (1993:June/July)
  - Box: 3, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Advocate, 1993; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.20:no.1 (1993:Sept.)
    - Item 2: Advocate, 1993; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.20:no.2 (1993:Oct.)
    - Item 3: Advocate, 1993; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.20:no.3 (1993:Nov./Dec.)
    - Item 4: Advocate, 1994; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.20:no.4 (1994:Jan.)
    - Item 5: Advocate, 1994; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.20:no.5 (1994:Feb.)
    - Item 6: Advocate, 1994; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.20:no.6 (1994:Mar.)
    - Item 7: Advocate, 1994; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.20:no.7 (1994:Apr.)
    - Item 8: Advocate, 1994; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.20:no.8 (1994:May)
    - Item 9: Advocate, 1994; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Notes: v.20:no.9 (1994:June/July)
    - Item 10: Advocate, 1994; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Notes: Special Edition (1994:Aug.)
  - Box: 3, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Advocate, 1994; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Notes: v.21:no.1 (1994:Sept.)
    - Item 2: Advocate, 1994; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Notes: v.21:no.2 (1994:Oct.)
    - Item 3: Advocate, 1994; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Notes: v.21:no.3 (1994:Nov./Dec.)
    - Item 4: Advocate, 1995; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Notes: v.21:no.4 (1995:Jan.)
    - Item 5: Advocate, 1995; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Notes: v.21:no.5 (1995:Feb.)
    - Item 6: Advocate, 1995; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Notes: v.21:no.5 (1995:Mar.)
    - Item 7: Advocate, 1995; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Notes: v.21:no.8 (1995:May)
    - Item 8: Advocate, 1995; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Notes: v.21:no.9 (1995:June/July)
  - Box: 3, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Advocate, 1995; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Notes: v.22:no.2 (1995:Oct.)
    - Item 2: Advocate, 1995; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Notes: v.22:no.3 (1995:Nov./Dec.)
    - Item 3: Advocate, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Notes: v.22:no.4 (1996:Jan.)
    - Item 4: Advocate, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Notes: v.22:no.5 (1996:Feb.)
    - Item 5: Advocate, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Notes: v.22:no.6 (1996:Mar.)
    - Item 6: Advocate, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Notes: v.22:no.7 (1996:Apr./May)
    - Item 7: Advocate, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Notes: v.22:no.8 (1996:June/July)
    - Item 8: Advocate, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Notes: Special Edition (1996:Aug.)
  - Box: 3, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Advocate, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Notes: v.23:no.1 (1996:Sept.)
    - Item 2: Advocate, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Notes: v.23:no.2 (1996:Oct.)
    - Item 3: Advocate, 1996; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Notes: v.23:no.3 (1996:Nov./Dec.)
    - Item 4: Advocate, 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Notes: v.23:no.4 (1997:Jan.)
    - Item 5: Advocate, 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Notes: v.23:no.5 (1997:Feb.)
    - Item 6: Advocate, 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Notes: v.23:no.6 (1997:Mar.)
    - Item 7: Advocate, 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Notes: v.23:no.7 (1997:Apr.)
    - Item 8: Advocate, 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Notes: v.23:no.8 (1997:May)
    - Item 9: Advocate, 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Notes: v.23:no.9 (1997:June/July)
  - Box: 3, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Advocate, 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Notes: v.24:no.1 (1997:Sept.)
    - Item 2: Advocate, 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Notes: v.24:no.2 (1997:Oct.)
    - Item 3: Advocate, 1997; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Notes: v.24:no.3 (1997:Nov./Dec.)
    - Item 4: Advocate, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Notes: v.24:no.4 (1998:Jan.)
    - Item 5: Advocate, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Notes: v.24:no.5 (1998:Feb.)
    - Item 6: Advocate, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Notes: v.24:no.6 (1998:Mar.)
    - Item 7: Advocate, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Notes: v.24:no.7 (1998:Apr.)
    - Item 8: Advocate, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Notes: v.24:no.9 (1998:June/July)
  - Box: 3, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Advocate, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.25:no.1 (1998:Sept.)
    - Item 2: Advocate, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.25:no.2 (1998:Oct.)
    - Item 3: Advocate, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.25:no.3 (1998:Nov./Dec.)
    - Item 4: Advocate, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.25:no.4 (1999:Jan.)
    - Item 5: Advocate, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.25:no.5 (1999:Feb.)
    - Item 6: Advocate, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.25:no.6 (1999:Mar.)
    - Item 7: Advocate, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.25:no.7 (1999:Apr.)
    - Item 8: Advocate, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.25:no.8 (1999:May)
    - Item 9: Advocate, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Notes: v.25:no.9 (1999:June/July)
  - Box: 3, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Advocate, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Notes: v.26:no.8 (2000:May)
    - Item 2: Advocate, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Notes: v.26:no.9 (2000:June/July)
    - Item 3: Advocate, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Notes: v.26:no.1 (1999:Sept.)
    - Item 4: Advocate, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Notes: v.26:no.2 (1999:Oct.)
    - Item 5: Advocate, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Notes: v.26:no.3 (1999:Nov./Dec.)
    - Item 6: Advocate, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Notes: v.26:no.4 (2000:Jan.)
    - Item 7: Advocate, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Notes: v.26:no.5 (2000:Feb.)
    - Item 8: Advocate, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Notes: v.26:no.6 (2000:Mar.)
    - Item 9: Advocate, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Notes: v.26:no.7 (2000:Apr.)
  - Box: 3, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: Advocate, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Notes: v.27:no.1 (2000:Sept.)
    - Item 2: Advocate, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Notes: v.27:no.2 (2000:Oct.)
    - Item 3: Advocate, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Notes: v.27:no.3 (2000:Nov./Dec.)
    - Item 4: Advocate, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Notes: v.27:no.4 (2001:Jan.)
    - Item 5: Advocate, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Notes: v.27:no.5 (2001:Feb.)
    - Item 6: Advocate, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Notes: v.27:no.6 (2001:Mar.)
    - Item 7: Advocate, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Notes: v.27:no.7 (2001:Apr.)
    - Item 8: Advocate, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Notes: v.27:no.8 (2001:May)
    - Item 9: Advocate, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Notes: v.27:no.9 (2001:June/July)
  - Box: 3, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Advocate, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Notes: v.28:no.1 (2001:Sept.)
    - Item 2: Advocate, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Notes: v.28:no.2 (2001:Oct.)
    - Item 3: Advocate, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Notes: v.28:no.3 (2001:Nov./Dec.)
    - Item 4: Advocate, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Notes: v.28:no.4 (2002:Jan.)
    - Item 5: Advocate, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Notes: v.28:no.5 (2002:Feb.)
    - Item 6: Advocate, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Notes: v.28:no.6 (2002:Mar.)
    - Item 7: Advocate, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Notes: v.28:no.7 (2002:Apr.)
    - Item 8: Advocate, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Notes: v.28:no.8 (2002:May)
    - Item 9: Advocate, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Notes: v.28:no.9 (2002:June/July)
  - Box: 3, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Advocate, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Notes: v.29:no.1 (2002:Sept.)
    - Item 2: Advocate, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Notes: v.29:no.2 (2002:Oct.)
    - Item 3: Advocate, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Notes: v.29:no.3 (2002:Nov./Dec.)
    - Item 4: Advocate, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Notes: v.29:no.4 (2003:Jan.)
    - Item 5: Advocate, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Notes: v.29:no.5 (2003:Feb.)
    - Item 6: Advocate, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Notes: v.29:no.6 (2003:Mar.)
    - Item 7: Advocate, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Notes: v.29:no.7 (2003:Apr.)
    - Item 8: Advocate, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Notes: v.29:no.8 (2003:May)
    - Item 9: Advocate, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Notes: v.29:no.9 (2003:June/July)
  - Box: 3, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: Advocate, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: v.30:no.1 (2003:Sept.)
    - Item 2: Advocate, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: v.30:no.2 (2003:Oct.)
    - Item 3: Advocate, 2003; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: v.30:no.3 (2003:Nov./Dec.)
    - Item 4: Advocate, 2004; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: v.30:no.4 (2004:Jan.)
    - Item 5: Advocate, 2004; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: v.30:no.5 (2004:Feb.)
    - Item 6: Advocate, 2004; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: v.30:no.6 (2004:Mar.)
    - Item 7: Advocate, 2004; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: v.30:no.7 (2004:Apr.)
    - Item 8: Advocate, 2004; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: v.30:no.8 (2004:May)
    - Item 9: Advocate, 2004; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Notes: v.30:no.9 (2004:June/July)
  - Box: 3, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Advocate, 2004; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Notes: v.31:no.1 (2004:Sept.)
    - Item 2: Advocate, 2004; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Notes: v.31:no.2 (2004:Oct./Nov.)
    - Item 3: Advocate, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Notes: v.31:no.3 (2004/2005:Dec./Jan.)
    - Item 4: Advocate, 2005; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Notes: v.31:no.4 (2005:Feb.)
    - Item 5: Advocate, 2005; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Notes: v.31:no.5 (2005:Mar.)
    - Item 6: Advocate, 2005; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Notes: v.31:no.6 (2005:Apr.)
    - Item 7: Advocate, 2005; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Notes: v.31:no.7 (2005:May/June)
  - Box: 3, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Advocate, 2005; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Notes: v.32:no.1 (2005:Sept.)
    - Item 2: Advocate, 2005; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Notes: v.32:no.2 (2005:Oct./Nov.)
    - Item 3: Advocate, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Notes: v.32:no.3 (2005/2006:Dec./Jan.)
    - Item 4: Advocate, 2006; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Notes: v.32:no.4 (2006:Feb.)
    - Item 5: Advocate, 2006; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Notes: v.32:no.5 (2006:Mar.)
    - Item 6: Advocate, 2006; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Notes: v.32:no.6 (2006:Apr.)
    - Item 7: Advocate, 2006; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Notes: v.32:no.7 (2006:May/June)
    - Item 8: Advocate, 2006; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Policy Manual - November 2006, Publication (Box 4CD)
- Policy Manual - November 2006, Publication (Box 5CD)
- Policy Manual - November 2006, Publication (Box 6CD)
- Box: 7, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Author: NYSUT
- Box: 7, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Box: 7, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Box: 7, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Box: 7, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1994; Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Box: 7, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Box: 8, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Box: 8, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2005; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Box: 8, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Box: 8, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2001-2003 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Box: 8, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Box: 8, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2000; Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Box: 9, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2002-2004 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Box: 9, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2005-2007 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Box: 9, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2006; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Box: 9, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Box: 9, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2006-2007 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Box: 9, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 2006-2007 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Box: 10, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Annual Assembly, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Author: New York State United Teachers
- Box: 10, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Annual Assembly Proceedings, 1974; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Box: 10, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Annual Representative Assembly, 1973; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Box: 10, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Teacher Salaries Contract Analysis, 1980-1983 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Box: 10, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Officers Report, 1976-1987 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Box: 10, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, 1987; Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Box: 10, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Explanation of Terms for Teacher Contract Analysis, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Box: 10, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Teacher Contract Analysis Report, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Box: 10, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Teacher Contract Analysis Explanation of Terms, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Box: 10, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Nassau Regional Office Salary Schedule, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Box: 10, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Rankings of Steps Salary Schedule, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Box: 10, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Rockland County School Districts Salary Schedule Data, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Box: 10, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Suffolk County School Districts Salary Schedule Data, 1982-1989 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Box: 10, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Suffolk-BOCES # 2 Salary Schedule Data, 1982-1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Box: 10, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Suffolk BOCES 3 Salary Schedule Data, 1982-1989 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Box: 10, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Town of Babylon Salary Schedule Data, 1982-1989 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Box: 10, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: BOCES Teacher Contract Analysis, 1973-1979 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Box: 10, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Teacher Contract Analysis, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Box: 10, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Teacher Contract Analysis, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Box: 11, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Teacher Contract Analysis Final Report, 1973-1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Box: 12, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Teacher Contract Analysis Final Report, 1975-1979 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Box: 12, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Teacher Contract Analysis Final Report Otsego-Steuben, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Box: 12, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Teacher Contract Analysis Final Report Suffolk-Yates, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Box: 12, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Teachers Contract Analysis Preliminary Report, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Box: 13, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Teacher Contract Analysis, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Box: 13, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Teacher Contract Analysis Summary, 1972-1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Box: 13, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Teacher Contracts Using the Consumer Price Index, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Box: 13, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Teacher Salary Schedule Rankings, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Box: 13, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Teachers Salary Schedule Increases, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Box: 13, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Teachers Salary Schedule Increases, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Box: 13, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Basic Financial Data in Major Operating School Districts in New York State, 1975-1981 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Box: 14, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Implementation of Actions, 1987; Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Box: 14, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Implementation of Actions, 1987-1998 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Box: 14, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Resolutions Adopted by the Representative Assembly, 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Box: 14, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Report on Actions, 1986-1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Box: 14, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Proposed Resolutions, 1973-1987 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Box: 14, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Proposed Resolutions and Constitutional Amendments, 1976-1987 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Box: 15, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Box: 15, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1996; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Box: 15, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1995; Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Box: 15, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Box: 15, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Box: 15, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1998; Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Box: 16, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1999; Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Notes: Sept.- Nov.
- Box: 16, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1999; Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Notes: Jan.- Dec.
- Box: 16, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1999; Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Notes: Jan.- Apr.
- Box: 16, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New york Teacher, 1975; Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Notes: June- Aug.
- Box: 16, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1975; Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Notes: May- June
- Box: 16, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1975; Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Notes: May
- Box: 17, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1975; Publication (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Notes: Oct.- Dec.
- Box: 17, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1975; Publication (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Notes: Oct.- Nov.
- Box: 17, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1975; Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Notes: Sept.- Oct.
  - 1975, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Notes: Sept.-Oct.
- Box: 17, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1976; Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Notes: March
- Box: 17, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1976; Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Notes: Feb.- March
- Box: 17, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: NewYork Teacher, 1976; Publication (Box 17, Folder 6)
    Notes: Jan.- Feb.
- Box: 18, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1976; Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Notes: Nov.- Dec.
- Box: 18, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1976; Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Box: 18, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1976; Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Box: 18, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1976; Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Notes: May- Aug.
- Box: 18, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1976; Publication (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Notes: April- May
- Box: 18, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1976; Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Notes: April
- Box: 19, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New york Teacher, 1977; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Box: 19, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1977; Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Box: 19, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1977; Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Notes: Jan.
- Box: 19, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1977; Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Notes: June- Oct.
- Box: 19, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1977; Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Box: 19, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1977; Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Box: 20, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1978; Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Notes: March- April
- Box: 20, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1978; Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Notes: Jan.- March
- Box: 20, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1977; Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Box: 20, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1978; Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Box: 20, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1978; Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Notes: June- Sept.
- Box: 20, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: New York Teacher, 1978; Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Box: 21, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)